Mount Chichibu
秩父山地
Hakkou Chuu, Taran Chuu, Jiko Chuu, Pan Chuu
发光虫  加长虫  自私虫  内衣虫
and many others...
还有很多其他的…
There are so many casualties in Saitama alone
光是在琦玉就有这么多伤亡
Hey, listen
我问妳们
You didn't forget our target, did you?
妳们没忘记我们的目的吧
Yes, Your Majesty
是的  女王大人
Our target
我们的目的
is to prevent human reproduction which requires
是阻饶地球人繁殖所需的
H-Energy and lead the energy to extinction
H能源之摄取并使其灭亡
then, to invade this planet
借此侵略这颗星球
Exactly
正是如此
If the humans face up to us, we're gonna lose
若与地球人正面冲突我们将寡不敌众
To achieve our goal
为了达成目的
first things first, we have to deal with the HXERO who hinders us
先想办法解决那些 妨碍我们的HXERO吧
Don't worry
请您放心
I have an elaborate plan to capture them all
我有一个能将他们一网打尽的好计划
Looking forward to your performance
期待妳们的表现
Lascivious fools
沉溺于肉欲的愚蠢人类们啊
One of your three desires
你们的三大欲望的其中之一
is approaching disappearance
消灭的日子也近在眼前了
SUPER HXEROS
弩级战队HXEROS
Episode 4 "Snow White and the Color of the Sky"
第四话"白雪公主与宇宙的颜色"
Finally, I got you, HXE WHITE
终于逮到妳了  HXE  WHITE
Come on, if you wanna survive
来吧  还想活命的话
tell me where your friends are
就将同伴们的所在地招出来吧
No way
这种事我绝对不会告诉妳的
Soft breasts
这里明明这这么柔软
but you are just tough as nails
嘴巴倒是坚固严守呢
Humans with a figure like yours
像妳们这种身材的人类
is our object
存在本身就是我们的规制对象
I'm gonna teach you a lesson
我要亲手好好教训教训妳
and you'll never be against us
让妳今后再也无法忤逆我们
Is anything over now?
到此为止了吗
Momoka, Sora, Hoshino, and Enjo
百花  小宙  星乃同学  炎城同学
I'm sorry
对不起
What're you doing, Rumba?
你在做什么  伦巴
It's all Rumba fault
真是的  都是因为伦巴
to bring me a weird dream
害我做了一场好奇怪的梦
Morning
早安
Excuse me, I wanna wash my face
借过一下  我洗个脸
Shirayuki
白雪?
the Senior High School Department of Saitama Girl's school
琦玉早乙女女子学院高中部
My heart is still beating so fast.
心脏现在还是跳得好快
Good morning, Maihime
早啊  舞姬
You wear orange today
今天是穿橘色
so it's Tuesday
所以今天是星期二啰
Stop making my panties your calendar
不要把别人的内裤当成日历啦
What if some other people sees them.
要是被其他人看见那该怎么办
Nothing's gonna happen
又不会怎么样
We are on campus right now
现在已经进到学校里面了啊
Oh, Chiya
千夜也真是的
Oh, didn't you wear your black leggings today?
对了  妳今天没穿黑色紧身裤吗
I was in a hurry to attend school
因为今天上学有点匆忙
Yes?
是吗
She's Hoya Chiya
她是保谷千夜
She's like a prince in this school
在这早乙女女子学院是王子般的存在
and my playmate
同时也是我的儿时玩伴
I have no talents but a strong reaction to sex, and in comparison
和除了能强烈感应色情以外 没有其他才能的我相比
Chiya is...
千夜她…
All done
大概就这样了吧
That's you, Chiya
不愧是千夜大人
Fantastic calligraphy.
书法写得真好
How about yours, Maihime
怎么样  舞姬妳…
When would you finish?
妳要磨到什么时候啊
Are you ok?
没事吧
You seem to be blushing today
妳今天脸好像有点红喔
Is it？
是这样吗
But I'm totally fine
不过我真的没有什么啊
You're pretending again
妳又在逞强了
Your feet must be numb, aren't they?
妳该不会是脚麻掉了吧
Sorry
抱歉
She's so beautiful
真是太美了
And her dance is amazing
千夜大人连舞都跳得这么好
In contrast
相较之下
Keep up with the beat, Shirayuki
妳没跟上节拍喔  白雪同学
I apologize
对不起
It hurts
好痛
Stop, stop
暂停暂停
Are you ok, Maihime
妳没事吧  舞姬
I'm fine
是
She makes trouble to Chiya
她又给千夜大人添麻烦了
I just couldn't stand this clumsy girl
受不了  笨手笨脚的
Forget it, Maihime
别放在心上  舞姬
One day, you're gonna
妳总有一天
find your talent
一定也能找到专长的
People just didn't get that
大家只是都不晓得
in fact, you do have a lot of advantages
妳其实也是有很多优点的
For example?
比方说呢
Like …
比方说…
You express and behave sentimentally
言行举止看起来很煽情
You have big boobs
还有胸部很大
and full butt
和安产型的屁股之类的
But they don't seem like strengths actually
怎么好像都有一点偏啊
Oh
对了
Or... you can try to join different clubs
不然妳就试着加入各式各样的社团看看吧
then
如此一来
you may be able to find out your new talents
说不定就能发现自己的新才能了
Nah, let it go
不  还是算了
If I join a club
我要是加入社团
people would get into trouble because of me
一定会给大家添麻烦的
Why do you keep being so humble
妳怎么老是这么谦卑啊
But I like your gentleness
不过我不讨厌妳的温柔喔
And I'm occupied with my part-time job after school
而且我放学后还得忙着打工
Well, now you should tell me
妳也差不多该告诉我
what kind of work you are doing
到底在打什么工了吧
No... I can't
这…这个我绝对不能说
Wait
等一下
My bento's gonna... -Tell me
便当要... -快点告诉我
Get ready for your death, Kisei Chuu
给我觉悟吧  规制虫
You must think that I am about to fail, huh
你一定以为把我逼入绝境了吧
I'm gonna show you my secret tentacle …
就让你见识我的秘密触手…
No, my secret skill
不  让你见识我的秘密手段吧
It is heard that someone suspicious broke into the campus just now
刚才据传有可疑人物入侵校园
All students please retreat to the gym
请全体学生前往体育馆避难
Again
再重复一次
There is someone suspicious...
刚才据传有可疑人物…
It's Kisei Chuu's reaction
这是规制虫的反应
So that means...
难道说
They asked us to retreat?
要我们避难?
For suspicious people? Why
为什么非得为了可疑人物
do we need to do that?
做到这种地步不可啊
That's weird, where's Maihime?
奇怪  舞姬呢
What are you doing?
妳做什么
You do appear, Kisei Chuu
妳果然现身了  规制虫
As long as I'm here
只要有我在这里
you could do nothing
就不会再让妳继续为所欲为
You are …
妳是…
HXEROS
HXEROS
Oh, then I can tell Ma'am something cheering
看来可以向女王陛下报告好消息了
Ma'am?
女王陛下?
What is that
这是怎么搞的
This is the same feeling
这种感觉
as what I experienced in my dream this morning
就和早上做的梦一样
No, no
不行不行
It was really dangerous
刚才真危险
The dream almost came true
早上的梦差点就要成真了
I feel terrible
好  好难受…
That sound is …
这声音难道是…
Enjo
炎城同学
Shirayuki
白雪
Why did you become like this
你怎么会变成这样
When I came to my sense, I turned into this
当我回过神来就变成这样了
I think
我猜想
the Kisei Chuu must have
那个规制虫一定拥有
an ability that can change a person she touched into one of her tentacles
将手碰到的人类变成触手的能力
that is to say, those tentacles are all …
也就是说那些触手全都是…
They may all be the students of this school
可能都是这间学校的学生
Exactly
正是如此
My skill is
我的能力就是
to change people who have absorbed H-Energy into my tentacles
将吸收过H能源的人类变成触手
and with these tentacles, I gain the H-Energy
就这样透过增加的触手吸收H能源
Then, I can do more
进一步将更多人类变成触手
I named it the Human Tentacles Plan
我将它取名为"人类全触手计划"
That really is a long-term plan
这计划未免也太长远了吧
Come on
来吧
Are you able to break this net and attack me?
妳有办法穿越这触手包围网 对我展开攻击吗
It's coming, Shirayuki
要来了  白雪
I can do it
我能够做到的事
I'm the only one who can do it
只有我能够办到的事
There would be no problem today
今天的我不会有问题的
I'll protect you all
我要守护学校的大家
"Lamaze Cannon"
"拉玛泽砲"
You... you made it
成  成功了
Enjo
炎  炎城同学
I'm sorry, Shirayuki
抱歉  白雪
There is a suspicious person
有可疑人物
Sorry
对不起
Are you fine, Shirayuki
妳没事吧  白雪同学
Yes
是  我没事
Though I don't know what's going on
虽然不太清楚是怎么回事
Maihime, it seems that you've found
舞姬  看来妳终于找到了呢
you own talent
属于妳自己的专长
Thank you
谢谢妳
What happened
刚才到底发生什么事了呢
I am Shimi Chuu
我是衣鱼虫
I won't allow any existence of erotica
我绝不容许色情书籍的存在
Enjo
炎城
About yesterday
关  关于昨天那件事
You mean... in my room
妳说在我房间的…
I didn't mean to
我那个时候真的是情非得已
um... I was in a mess
或者应该说是我一时混乱
Anyway, that was not the real me
总而言之那并不是真正的我
Got it?
知道了吗
Yes, you should take a step back right now
我知道了  妳先离远一点吧
You …
你…
What the hell are you thinking about
你到底在想什么啊
Hentai
变态
What about you?
妳还不是也一样
I found it
找到了
The Ideal "H" eroine
理想的"H"eroine(女主角)
What the heck is she doing
那  那孩子搞什么啊
What's wrong
怎么了吗
So it seems
看样子
Sora likes you very much
小宙好像很喜欢妳的样子呢
Is that what she meant
她那原来是这个意思吗
I'm not sure
这点我也不是很清楚
Yeh
就是说啊
Momoka
百花
She
那家伙
appears to always stay in her room, drawing something
好像常窝在房间里画什么东西
But she never shows us
不过她从来没给我们看过就是了
We need more time to know each other
我们要了解彼此还需要一点时间
But as long as we could make friends in the future
不过大家以后只要能成为朋友
it's gonna be a happy life
这里的生活一定也会变得很开心的
You're right
说得也是
Since I'm gonna live here
既然要在这里生活
I need to know more about the others
我就得多了解其他人才行
Soymilk
豆浆
Let's share this and get along well with each other
那我们一起喝这个  大家好好相处吧
That's …
那是…
Is it ok to drink that?
喝那个东西没问题吗
What are you two talking about？
妳们两个到底在说什么
Showing your attitude that you don't need to have it because you have large boobs
一副胸部很大没有必要喝的态度
Shit-Wait
可恶 -等一下
Like …
像这样…
Oh
真是的
Momoka
百花
Sorry
抱歉
Stop licking there
不可以舔那种地方
Come on
上吧
Go, Rumba, go
快上吧  伦巴
Anyhow
总而言之
this is what Taoyuan and Shirayuki are like
桃园同学和白雪同学就是这样的人吧
This is...
这是…
Y-You saw？
妳  妳看到了吗
Sorry
对不起
I didn't mean to peek
我没有要偷看的意思
The notebook was on the floor
我只是看到笔记本掉在地上
and I wanted pick it up, but...
打算捡起来  然后就…
Anyway you're good at drawing, Tenkuzi
不过天空寺同学的画画得真好
No one in this house has seen them yet
我都还没给这个家的任何人看过
Now that you know
既然被发现了
I have to take embarrassing pictures of you to keep you silence
就只好拍下云母难为情的样子 好让妳住嘴了
What? Why?
为什么变成这样啊
Because I know
因为我都知道
the source of Sora's H energy is different from others'
就只有宙的H能源源头和大家不一样
And I know it's weird
我也知道很奇怪
But I like it too much to stop
但就是因为喜欢所以才停不下来
When I settled back down to my conciousness, I was painting myself
回过神来时连自己也开始画画了
If they all know it, I'm sure I'm gonna be laughed at
大家要是知道了一定会笑我的
No
没有这回事
Everybody has a secretive interesting or past
不管是谁都有不可告人的兴趣或过去
Me, too
我也有过这样的经验
So I can understand how you feel
所以能理解妳的心情
So
所以说
there is no reason for you to stop.
根本没有勉强自己停笔的理由啊
Besides
还有就是
before you're ready to tell others
在妳能自己说出口之前
I won't say a word
我都不会告诉其他人的
I promise you
我和妳保证
Ok?
好吗
Ok, I forgive you now
我知道了  那我原谅妳
But...
但是相对的
since you've seen my most embarrasing things
既然宙最难为情的东西被看见了
I wanna see yours
那宙也要看云母难为情的一面
Is it...
现在这该不会是…
The image of the character which I'm drawing in my manga
我现在正在画的漫画角色
is perfectly fitted by you
形象就和云母一模一样
I can't do it well unless I see the real things
如果没看过实体 果然没办法画得很好
So that's what it meant
当时那个原来是这个意思吗
I can't see them well with your sheet there
用床单遮着我看不清楚
Ok
我知道了
If my body could help you
如果不嫌弃我的身体
refer to it as you want
妳就尽管拿去当参考吧
Really?
真的吗
Then...
那么…
Sora?
小宙?
What do you want me to do with the flute
妳给我这支直笛要我做什么呢
Umm
那个
I want to draw a picture that a clumsy girl slips
我想画冒失的女孩子滑倒
with a flute between her boobs and I want your help as a reference
直笛夹在胸部中间的场面 希望有模特儿当参考
So, put it between your breasts
把它夹在胸部间吧
What kind of manga is it?
哪门子的漫画啊
For example
比方说
Enjo
炎  炎城
I can't stand it any more
我再也忍不住了
I was in the next room
我明明就在隔壁房间
and Hoshino was naked here
星乃却脱得光溜溜的
You are tempting me to come here, aren't you?
就摆明就是在诱惑我吧
You brought it on
给我负起责任
It's this kind of manga
就是这种感觉的漫画
Briefly, erotica
简单讲就是色色的漫画吧
So she could express in this way? !
这女孩原来也会露出这种表情吗
What?
怎么了
Emergency alert, emergency alert
发布紧急警报  发布紧急警报
A Kisei Chuu has appeared at the bookshop in town
街道上的书店有规制虫出没
And please go ahead immediately, HXEROS
请HXEROS现在即刻出动
Let's go, Kirara
我们走吧  云母
Get ready
赶快做准备吧
Did you hear that?
听见了吗  刚才的…
Knock on the door at least when you barge into a girl's room
为什么进女生的房间门都不先敲一下啊
So here is the bookshop where provides a mass of erotica
这家店就是提供人类 大量猥亵书籍的店吧
Why would it be at such an unnoticeable spot
虽然不晓得为什么会选上这种不起眼的地点
But according to Ma'am, it should all be censored
基于女王陛下的意志  我要进行规制
Go! My bugs!
去吧  小虫们
What's happening?
怎  怎么会这样
Protect the people outside, Momozono and Shirayuki
外面的人就交给桃园和白雪了
Ok
是
We count on you
拜托你们了
What's this?
这是怎么回事
What's wrong, Tenkuzi?
怎么了  天空寺
This is my favorite bookstore
这家店是宙很喜欢的书店
And they are destroying it
牠们竟然做了这种事
they would pay for it
不可原谅
Tenkuzi
天空寺
HXEROS
HXEROS
You, deal with them
拦住他们  剩下就交给你们了
She escaped
逃走了
I'll seize her
那家伙就交给我
But I have no idea what to do
我还没办法对付牠们啦
It's ok
不要紧的
Sora, you are...
小宙  妳这身模样是…
It is my XERO GEAR
这是宙的XERO  GEAR
enboding my H-Energy in wings
将H能源具现化为翅膀的样子
You can do this? !
原来还能做到这种事吗
As long as you can imagine that
只要能明确地进行想像
it's really easy
这其实很简单的
But
不过
we're surrounded by too many enemies
现在敌人的数量实在太多了
There is still someone here
店里还有人在
Thank you
谢谢妳
Are you all right, Kirara?
妳没事吧  云母
Even though I could use my power
就算无法使用能力
I could do that at least
这点小事我也还是办得到的
Let me handle it
接下来就交给宙吧
Retreat with her
快带着这个人离开吧
Come on, follow me
来  走这边
Ok
是
Thank you, Kirara
谢谢妳  云母
My drawings
我画的那些图
haven't been seen by anyone because of my embarrassment
因为太难为情都不曾给别人看过
But it felt so great to be praised
原来被人称赞是那么舒服的事
So... they...
所以说…大家才会…
Solar Ray
"天空的闪光"
Well done, Sora
小宙好厉害喔
Yeh, truly
是啊  辛苦妳了
Retto
烈人
Tenkuzi, where are your clothes
天空寺  妳的替换衣物呢
Never mind... Kirara was
先不说这个  云母她…
She was
云母她被…
Your Majesty
女王陛下
We successfully
我们顺利将HXEROS之中
captured a harmless member of HXEROS
唯一推测无害的成员掳为人质了
Have you told her our demand?
有将要求传达给对方了吗
Yes
有的
If she don't want her H-Energy totally taken out
如果不希望这人类的H能源被吸收殆尽
bring her companions here
就带着同伴过来这里
Great job
做得非常好
Then
那么
Let's go get prepared for it
现在就去准备展开迎击吧
Once HXEROS can be eliminated
只要能排除HXEROS
the plan can go further
计划就可以迈向下一个阶段了
to castrate humans through regulation
透过规制将人类去势
Wait for me, Hoshino
妳等我  星乃
SUPER HXEROS
弩级战队HXEROS
The next episode "HXEROS. RISING"
下一回"HXEROS．RISING"